<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-02-05T22:12:38+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My Blog</title><subtitle>Personal Blog</subtitle><author><name>Abhinav Sharma</name></author><entry><title type="html">How to choose bride/groom in Indian Marriages</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Indian_marriage/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to choose bride/groom in Indian Marriages" /><published>2018-10-02T10:44:47+05:30</published><updated>2018-10-02T10:44:47+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Indian_marriage</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Indian_marriage/">&lt;p&gt;Choosing a life partner is a very hard decision a person has to make in his/her life. In India, especially in past, this decision was taken by the parents. But as the society is getting modern, this decision is taken by person getting married. Now I am not talking about love-marriage here. I am specifically talking about modern arrange marriages, in which one has to decide from a single meeting whether a person is fit for them for entire life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of you are wondering how is this possible. How can one make a decision for lifetime in just a single meeting. The answer is, this is a gamble. But you can focus on few points, so that the game may come in your favor. Please note that good education, money, property, government job, all these materialistic things do not matter when taking a decision of marriage. You yourself might have many examples of elderly couple around you who were nothing when they married but later acquired all the things that you want now. And you can easily agree with me that these things can also disappear after marriage. Then only thing that will matter after marriage is love, understanding and a little will to adjust with each other. There is no perfect human being. Even if there is, then is very hard to find. But the good thing is, if a person is perfect, you will know immediately. Because of the vibes that person will send. Same is true if the person is extremely imperfect for you. And these both kind of persons are rare. This is easy to identify. The behavior peoples follow this famous Bell Curve [Bell] on an average. This means that most of the people have good type of behavior. Yeah, I know you may argue that the whole world is full of morons and crappy people but believe me. If you look closely, most of them are nice people (or average).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So my only advice is not have any bias whatsoever based on the materialistic background of the person you are going to visit. Treat them respectfully and ask whether they will treat you and your family the same. Most of the urban couples are working, but still if for any reason you want your better half to be house-husband or house-wife, then clearly talk to them about their preferences. There is no need to talk about your Ex or their Ex in any meeting. Let the past quietly
buried in the past. Be loyal if you are committed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a Good luck&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Abhinav Sharma</name></author><category term="Indian Marriages" /><category term="Arranged Marriage" /><category term="life partner" /><summary type="html">My thoughts about chosing a life partner in Indian Arranged Marriages</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My First Blog</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/My-first-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My First Blog" /><published>2017-02-27T10:44:47+05:30</published><updated>2017-02-27T10:44:47+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/My-first-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/My-first-blog/">&lt;p&gt;As the title says, this is my first ever blog. I have never been into writing. I do write codes and occasionally improvise documents of my friends but have never been into writing stuff from my mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my new experiment to which I remember I wanted to do from a very long time. I wish to write weekly blog about the things I read and things I feel to share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To finish this quick short and first blog I would like to share the thought&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am using &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;github pages&lt;/a&gt; to make and host this blog. I do agree that it is pretty simple and straight forward. But still I messed up in the start. Nevertheless, its setup and all done for good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. Also, you can follow any tutorial to get started.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Abhinav Sharma</name></author><summary type="html">The journey of thousand miles starts with a small step.</summary></entry></feed>